4/25/2020 Alexander Watson

ALEXANDER WATSON

CMO, PROJECT LEAD

Download PDF

<u>alexander.watson1019@gmail.com</u> (256) - 339 - 3726

Profile

Actively engaging customers through sleek, modern ad design. Leading teams towards shared goals, with an emphessis on discussion.

Skills

Marketing

Reaching target audiences through well researched ad copy, and engaging media.

Product Creation

Leading and directing multiple teams towards simple, effective and cost effective solutions.

Project Direction

Proven ability to lead and manage a wide variety of design and development projects in team and independent situations.

Technical

XHTML	Jquery	OS X
CSS	PHP	Windows XP/Vista
Javascript	CVS / Subversion	Linux

Experience

GM8.app

Corporate Marketing Officer

At GM8 I work tirelessly to attract customers through the use of effective ad copy, engaging media, and researched targeting.

Wevape.shop

2016-2019t

2017-2019

Head of Logistics

At Wevape.shop I activly manage shipping of all products ordered by our customers, working to make sure all asspects of shipping are handled with speed and care.

Rusken Packaging

2016-Present

Machine Operator

At Rusken I lead a team of hardworking individuals in the production or made to order cardboard packaging.

Education

WestPoint Highschool - WestPoint, Alabama Standard Diploma — **3.4 GPA**

Alexander Watson — $\underline{\text{alexander.watson1019@gmail.com}}$ — (256) - 339 - 3726